<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Michael &amp; Friska</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/</link><description>Recent content on Michael &amp; Friska</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://michael-friska.liondy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zenna Office &amp; Home Living</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/zenna/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/zenna/</guid><description/></item><item><title>PT Gundjaya Abadi</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/gundjaya/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/gundjaya/</guid><description>PT Gundjaya Abadi is a convection company which is based in Bandung. In 2023, the owner of the convection wanted Michael to develop their internal application program. This program was intended to manage their massive pre-order apparel. With this system, it hopes to simplify the order process of PT Gundjaya Abadi. The program has three main features. The first thing is to store customer&amp;rsquo;s order data. The second thing is it can generates the invoice so that the staff can give the price immediately after booking complete with down payment and full payment info.</description></item><item><title>BJB Salmon</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/bjbsalmon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/bjbsalmon/</guid><description>A lot of things could be taken fromt this project. The first thing was being able to learn new things fast. Michael was able to perform learning by doing because he only used React Javascript before and never used these language (Nest &amp;amp; Next Typescript) which was the framework of React. Michael also learned the process of devops. This was the first time he performed devops in a real project. The second thing was Michael learned to perform actions in a team.</description></item><item><title>Werkules ERP Solution</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/werkules/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/werkules/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Our First Anniversary</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/blog/our-first-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/blog/our-first-anniversary/</guid><description>Uh&amp;hellip;.isn&amp;rsquo;t it cute?
This is our dinner anniversary
This is us</description></item><item><title>MTBS</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/mtbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/mtbs/</guid><description>Friska eventually managed to develop the website. She had to learn React JS and now she is capable to develop website using React JS. This project was a one-year contract and finally Friska did it. Unfortunately, the website was not hosted yet so we will update this section later :)</description></item><item><title>Port Scanning Detection SDN Application</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/port-scan-detection-sdn-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/port-scan-detection-sdn-app/</guid><description>This project was for Michael&amp;rsquo;s undergraduate thesis. He developed two kinds of application. One is a Python script to crawl network packets and the other is a web application to display port scanning activities. This application could not be hosted because the web application requires the Python script. This Python script must run in a SDN network environment.
Michael provides an open-source code in his Github too: https://github.com/liondy/SDN-Port-Scan-Detector</description></item><item><title>Covid-19 Tracker Website</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/covid19-tracker-website/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/covid19-tracker-website/</guid><description>This project was for another college project guided by Michael. He propose a covid-19 tracker website to help people know their current location situation. It runs well and was hosted under liondy.com(a domain for Michael Liondy). The website can be seen in: https://covid19tracker.liondy.com/
Michael provides an open-source code in his Github too: https://github.com/liondy/covid19-tracker-website</description></item><item><title>Markdown Formatting Demo</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/blog/markdown-formatting-demo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/blog/markdown-formatting-demo/</guid><description>This example Markdown file compliments of markdown-it.github.io
h1 Heading 8-) h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Horizontal Rules Typographic replacements Enable typographer option to see result.
(c) (C) (r) (R) (tm) (TM) (p) (P) +-
test.. test&amp;hellip; test&amp;hellip;.. test?&amp;hellip;.. test!&amp;hellip;.
!!!!!! ???? ,, &amp;ndash; &amp;mdash;
&amp;ldquo;Smartypants, double quotes&amp;rdquo; and &amp;lsquo;single quotes&amp;rsquo;
Emphasis This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text</description></item><item><title>BUMDes Banjaran</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/bumdes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/bumdes/</guid><description>Michael developed this website using Code Igniter 4. This project was Michael&amp;rsquo;s first real project outside of college assignments or his initiative. During this project, Michael got a lot of help from Friska especially in designing the homepage UI. The website has been published in 2020 but was no longer maintained so we cannot see the live action of the website. Sorry :(
Because this project and website belongs to client, we cannot provide an open-source source code :)</description></item><item><title>Covid-19 Tracker Mobile</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/covid-tracker-mobile/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/covid-tracker-mobile/</guid><description>This project was initiated by Michael to help people see real-time data statistic of covid-19 from all around the world. This project was built with React Native (a Javascript Framework). This app was published to APK Store: https://www.apkfiles.com/apk-600295/covid-19-tracker
The app was published to APK Store because Google Play refused to published application related to covid-19 as there was no application for tracking covid-19 from hospital or government back then. For those who wanted to see the source code, it is available in Michael&amp;rsquo;s Github: https://github.</description></item><item><title>Bebras Application</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/bebras-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/bebras-app/</guid><description>This project was for college project that was built by 3 team person. This project was built with React Native (a Javascript Framework). For some reason, this application was never published to Play Store because Michael and the team were unable to dynamically add the questions from outside of code. Because of this, if school commitee wants to add questions to package, it will be difficult.
For those who wanted to see the source code, it is available in Michael&amp;rsquo;s Github: https://github.</description></item><item><title>iFirstRow</title><link>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/ifirstrow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michael-friska.liondy.com/portfolio/ifirstrow/</guid><description>Friska and Michael both success taking this project. Because this website emphasizes on ui/ux, it was not hosted on the internet. We provide the open-source code in Friska&amp;rsquo;s Github: https://github.com/friskac/projectimk</description></item></channel></rss>